[
  { "question": "1*1", "answer": 1 },
  { "question": "1*2", "answer": 2 },
  { "question": "1*3", "answer": 3 },
  { "question": "1*4", "answer": 4 },
  { "question": "1*5", "answer": 5 },
  { "question": "1*6", "answer": 6 },
  { "question": "1*7", "answer": 7 },
  { "question": "1*8", "answer": 8 },
  { "question": "1*9", "answer": 9 },
  { "question": "1*10", "answer": 10 },
  { "question": "2*1", "answer": 2 },
  { "question": "2*2", "answer": 4 },
  { "question": "2*3", "answer": 6 },
  { "question": "2*4", "answer": 8 },
  { "question": "2*5", "answer": 10 },
  { "question": "2*6", "answer": 12 },
  { "question": "2*7", "answer": 14 },
  { "question": "2*8", "answer": 16 },
  { "question": "2*9", "answer": 18 },
  { "question": "2*10", "answer": 20 }
]
